number
nine Insurance credential supervision
Bill committee stage I declare the house
and committee for consideration of the
insurance Prudential supervision Bill Mr
Speaker Mr
chairman hang on just one just one
moment members the house and committee
on the insurance credential supervision
board Mr I call Joe good you I seek
leave of the house to have all parts of
the insurance presedential supervision
Amendment Bill taken as one question
leave a sort for that purpose is there
any
objection there is no
objection members the question is that
Parts 1 to 5 schedules 1: 3 and clauses
one and two stand
part the chair The Honorable Nathan guy
sure I think it's appropriate to
acknowledge uh this bill has good cross
Party Support it had its first reading